Okay, now let's start making the pants.
To make the pants, first of all,
I made this style,
which is a relatively vintage suit.
Its pants,
especially in the 20th century,
their pants are all high waist pants.
All high waist pants.
So here we pull the pants up along the vertical direction.
Make it a little higher waist.
At this time, if you directly simulate,
we just saw that the pants fell down.
Because you are on the spot, right?
We are pulling directly above the vertical direction.
Then the waist of the person is,
because you are high waist,
the higher the waist, the thinner the waist, right?
Because if you normally wear pants,
your,
your pants are definitely not as thin as your waist.
So we want to change this version.
First of all,
this waist has been worn relatively high.
We don't need to wear a belt first.
We want to change this version,
so that its waist is in harmony with the body.
Yes, in fact,
this Gouda Gouda Gouda is right.
It's this belt pants.
In fact,
the belt pants are just a small comparison with everyone.
In fact, wearing belt pants is more formal in the suit.
That is, if you want to do it,
that is, if you want to wear it more flat,
or if you just want to wear a relatively deep style,
you must still have two straps.
Of course, this is not to say that it is a rule,
but in general, it is like this.
Because you only wear that,
that belt elastic belt,
it can be worn to the appropriate position.
It's not easy to just,
just swing around.
Of course, we can't do it because we can't see it here.
This is an exception.
Let me tell you.
Then I saw the wind and fire.
He said he wanted to learn this light-weight suit.
In fact, you learn,
you see,
our daily live broadcast is almost the same.
Do you understand?
Well,
then we are here.
Tell you about it.
We usually change clothes.
Anyway, I personally change clothes.
I'll tell you again about my usual habit of changing clothes.
First of all, let's look at this pair of pants.
Did this pair of pants fall down just now?
Right?
If it falls down,
what is the reason?
Is it because his waist is wider than the model's waist here?
I'm looking at it from the front,
so you can't see it.
If you pull it to the side,
you will see it here.
It's this plate here.
It has a multiple overlap part.
The waist on his side also has a multiple part,
right?
But is his hip here not much?
So in fact,
it's just his waist here that's a lot.
Can you understand?
Yes,
it's a live broadcast.
Hello,
The waist here is wider,
so we don't have to change the part below the hip.
This pair of pants will fall down.
It has nothing to do with this hip.
It has a bigger relationship with this waist.
So we add two points in the hip here.
If you don't know where the hip is,
you can click on the plate.
Just find the position of the hip
according to the blue index point.
After finding the position of the hip,
let's take a look at how to find that point.
I should have clicked here.
See?
I clicked it.
You can find that the hip is almost in this position.
Yes.
To be precise,
it's the hip line.
Yes.
But you're not so...
You just need to know about it.
Yes.
Here is the hip line.
Because we usually change the hip line and the knee.
After adding two points here,
these two points will not be affected
if we click below the breakpoint.
Because it doesn't affect it,
we can move this point of the waist in a little bit.
Then our waist will be tightened.
You can see that it won't fall down.
So when you're doing it,
especially when you're making pants,
it's best to follow my rhythm.
If you don't want to affect it below,
you just break it.
Adding more straight lines is not wrong.
Can you understand?
Is MD used more in the fashion industry?
No.
MD is used more in the fashion industry.
The clothing industry uses another software of our company,
called Close.
They also have an official channel.
You can also pay attention to it.
Hello, good evening.
Okay.
Now we have solved the problem
that the pants will fall down.
Right?
Because we just tightened the waist here separately.
If you don't add this point of the straight line on the side,
if you move this waist,
the whole side will be affected by it.
This is also why we need to add this point of the straight line.
Then we draw a belt with the inner line.
Then cut and sew it.
Okay.
Now we have the belt.
We're going to start making the pants.
First of all,
let's make the point of the bottom.
I moved the point of the bottom up a little bit.
Because we look at the point of the bottom from the side,
it's actually a little bit down.
In general,
the suit pants won't be very loose and wide.
Even if it's a wide-leg pants,
the point of the bottom won't be particularly down.
We just say that it falls down.
The point of the break is X.
Okay.
Then we put the pants.
Because I'll show you the final result.
This is the final result.
You can see that
even though it's a wide-leg pants,
it's still in the normal position.
Otherwise,
if the point of the bottom falls down too much,
it won't look very neat.
Generally speaking,
we don't have to worry about it.
The point of the bottom is still in the normal position.
Otherwise,
if the point of the bottom falls down too much,
it won't look very neat.
Generally speaking,
we don't have to worry about it.
the point of the bottom of the pants
is just like the point of the pants
of the normal pants.
It won't be too much different.
Because if it falls down again,
it looks like a more modern pants.
Then,
there is another wide-leg pants.
This is the point of our hips, right?
We just took the pants.
Is it a tight state here at the corner of the foot?
Then we have to do the wide-leg pants.
just move the two points to the same position as the hip joint.
Do you see the pink reference line?
Move it over so that you can widen the side.
The hip joint point is also a reference point.
Then the point on the inside, you use the point on the waist as a reference point.
Now your pants are more or less relaxed, right?
One more thing, everyone always says that my pants are very loose,
but I don't have a wrinkle here, right?
Sometimes it's because you didn't figure it out.
In fact, our pants look loose, but they are loose below the hip joint.
The hip joint is still attached in most cases,
because it has to have that strength to form a wrinkle.
Do you understand?
Yes, we are official, we are Marvelous Designers official.
Everyone can pay attention to our live broadcast.
Can you understand?
No matter if your pants are loose, your pants have to be tight to form a wrinkle.
So we are tight in the upper part,
and we change it to the lower part.
This is also my question.
Why do you say that the side of your pants should have this breakpoint?
Do you understand?
Can everyone understand?
Okay, the baby who understands can say a word.
Ah, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
Yes.
Then, for example, we now widen the whole side, right?
It's more relaxed now.
It's more relaxed.
If it's more relaxed,
but when it's relaxed,
does it have more volume here?
Right?
Well, we usually wear this kind of particularly loose sports pants.
Because sports pants have a lot of creases.
But you need to have creases here in the suit pants.
It's this kind of vertical creases.
Because we want to make the pants wider,
it must be here.
You can't escape in the end.
You have to bring the whole side line out.
It's enough to pull it out.
Otherwise, it becomes a lullaby.
Right?
Because we're going to make it straight on the side now.
The side of the suit pants is usually straight like this.
It's either in real life.
Unless you wear a lullaby.
Otherwise, these two points will not exceed.
It's this point and this point.
It's on the vertical direction.
Okay, so we're going to.
You can't do anything now.
We just have to widen the side.
Okay, so we're going to widen the side.
Let's take a look at this.
It's the final product.
I have a line in the final product.
Right?
There's usually this fold line in the suit pants.
Then we can use a method.
We can make a fold here.
Hide this amount in.
Plus we have these out there.
It's okay to wear a suit.
Because we'll talk about suits later.
It's okay to wear a vest.
Hide this part.
It's the fold position.
Hide it.
Okay.
We can do this.
So we're also laying here.
At the same time.
He has enough amount of pants here.
And because we have a fold here.
So you see.
We're still here.
The fold here.
He still has it.
It's in some of your actions.
He still has the fold in his hands.
Right?
Okay, then we're going to do that next.
Okay, the fold.
First of all.
It's like this.
We're wearing this belt.
Look, our belt certainly hopes that it will not be dragged down by the heavier pants.
So let's apply a new fabric to the belt.
I won't pull the belt down first.
Do you know which fabric we are going to use here?
The name of this fabric is relatively long.
Do you know which fabric we are going to use?
What we are going to do now is to give this belt a fabric
so that the belt will not be dragged down by the heavier pants,
which will cause the belt to deform.
In other words, we are now going to apply a fabric that does not easily deform to the belt.
If you don't show the small window,
it may be because you used the previous version.
This is updated in a pudding version of Marvelous Designer 11.
Ah, I see that many children
have on underpants already.
Good, no underpants.
You can't just pull it down down just because of my logo
and think it's underpants.
As for underpants,
It is a multi-r governmental fabric.
It doesn't produce cuadrittoes easily,
but its tendons, dietae, strength and foreheadPod are longaxial,
right in the middle.
It's small, isn't it?
Hardeners don't burn. Hardeners also have a higher bending strength.
It's also not easy to get cramps.
But can it...
Can it...
Is it easy to stretch? It's a different nature.
If you are cold, you can do it.
But if you are cold, you can't wear pants.
The belt will always be cold, right?
In the end, you still have to participate in the simulation.
If you are in the cold,
For example, we are going to change the movement.
Is it still not working?
Of course, you use the leather.
Then fix the needle and fix it to the virtual model.
It's okay.
But are we going to wear these pants outside the shirt?
Since he wants to wear it outside the shirt,
Then he can't use the needle directly to the virtual model.
Because there must be a layer in the middle.
This shirt.
If you choose to fix it to the virtual model,
Hey, that's not right.
What about the shirt?
Right?
Okay, then we...
The fabric we are going to use here is the Trim Fusible Origin.
This fabric is actually a sticky fabric.
We usually wear pants in real life.
There will be a...
There will be a hem in the belt.
This hem is a composite fabric.
Make this belt harder.
It's not easy to transform.
Understand?
Everyone remembers this Fusible Origin.
Let's take a look at it.
The specific physical properties of the fabric.
Physical properties.
It's this fabric.
Wait a minute.
Fusible Origin.
Let's take a look at the physical properties of this fabric.
It has a very high end-to-end strength.
This proves that this is a fabric that does not stretch easily.
Since it doesn't stretch easily,
it will not cause it to deform due to these forces of gravity.
That's why we use this fabric every time we use a belt.
Remember, everyone.
Next time we'll test it.
Thank you, Tatika, for supporting me so much.
Are you my colleague?
Thank you.
Your speech is a bit like my colleague.
After we change the fabric, you can see the effect immediately, right?
Let's take a closer look.
Can you see it?
Originally, the belt will fall down, but now it looks tight and will not deform.
This is why we use this fabric, so that it will not deform due to external forces.
Fusible Rigid's Chinese should be called Fusible Rigid.
I didn't translate it.
I didn't translate it in my impression.
It may be called Nianchen.
It's his Chinese.
Or even if you don't use this fabric, you can make another piece of fabric separately.
Increase the strength of the gold veneer and the tension of the foot line.
Then increase the bending strength a little bit.
It's the same.
In fact, we are the main purpose.
The core purpose.
Make it difficult for it to deform.
Understand?
Otherwise, it will be pulled down by the pants.
OK?
Then we freeze the board.
You can freeze the board habitually.
We also pull the pants of the other part a little wider.
Next, we will start to do the pleating part.
The part of pleating.
It may look a little troublesome here.
But let me tell you the principle.
First of all, we have the length difference of the sewing line.
Right?
Let's take a look at the length difference.
It's about 50.
Then do we have to jump the 50th section in the middle?
So we have to draw two lines.
Three lines in total.
The distance between the two lines is 25.
So after we fold the middle section in half,
the length difference of 50 is eaten.
Oh, it's over.
I usually do the fabric.
I did it manually.
Then we align to the play-on line.
And then we delete this VM line.
We come step by step.
First of all, the length difference is 50.
So the distance between the two lines is 25.
Then we turn this fold tool.
From the middle to the outside, click from the left side of the first inner line to the right side of the last inner line and double-click to confirm.
Then we press the control key to simulate it, and then we press the control key to simulate it.
Because the fabric used in our pants is soft fabric, first of all, we have a number here.
The number of inner lines of each fold should be 3, not 2, because we are a group of three roots, so we must choose 3.
So it is 0, 360, 180 from left to right, it is just the number of a pair of folds.
Then we press the control key to simulate it, because the fabric is soft, so when you simulate it, it will automatically pull down.
Then we press the control key to simulate it, after dementia, it will slowly pull up.
The fold angle with this part is relatively obvious.
Then we make ourrivations, using this free-re kanske tool.
One end after the other, we closed it.
Now we start sewing our wear.
okay, Miso is done, please remove your Rubick pouch.
i have a box.
sorry i miss our Bree.
Draw it out as a book. okay?
Start from the middle, left and right, and then turn the sewing line into a turn, and then sew it up.
Then we look for this 360-degree line, sew it up, and then turn the sewing line into a turn, and then we're done with the fold.
Then unsew the hardening. After unsewing the hardening, we use this free sewing to sew the whole belt first, and then press the Shift key.
Because we have to skip the fold in the middle, right?
Our point, because it's folded in the middle, so we skip this fold.
There's a loop, there's a loop, and then we start sewing from this 360-degree point to the side.
Okay, and then press the Shift key to model.
Okay, so after we've modeled it, is our waist very flat here?
Because we skipped the 50-degree difference in the middle and sewed it together, so it's flat now.
And its bottom is here, the amount that should be there is still there.
Then if we sew it, it will use a shank to transport a very obvious protruding line.
Then we just have to extend this 0-degree bright red line to the bottom.
Did you see that this line is facing the outside, the panel is facing the outside.
So we're going to set it to a fold angle of 0 degrees.
And when you turn on the space simulation, you will see that this very obvious fold of the suit is coming out.
Okay, so we can move this panel.
And then it's not moving the panel, it's moving this line.
Because just now we changed the entire pants.
Before we changed, we changed the curve on the outside, right?
So the whole pants, it's actually a little crooked.
It's a little crooked in its orientation.
So we started to change it.
So we look like we're adding this shape line in the vertical direction.
In fact, it's not vertical in 3D space.
Then we can move it to the side according to the need.
Do you understand?
In addition, we just looked at this pants.
Is it bent inwards?
Here you will see it bent inwards and then protrude again.
Then we delete the curve points of these two lines.
Let it form a straight line point.
In this way, it will become a straight pants.
Right?
You see, this pants is now straight.
When it becomes straight,
we will extend this line to the outside of the panel.
It is now in the middle line here.
Then because we refer to this middle line,
is it that there is less fabric on the inside here?
You can see it clearly.
Here it is pasted, here it is less, here it is more.
We just move this point out a little bit.
Give it this amount.
Do you understand?
In addition, we just have this pants.
First of all, you have to make it bright.
Then you look at the whole pants.
We use the waist level position of the waist as the basis.
Are these two points a little bit to the right?
It's not in the middle.
The left and right are more symmetrical.
So we choose these two points here.
Move it a little bit.
Move it all the way to the middle.
Make it look like it's symmetrical left and right.
Like this.
Then the back is also adjusted in the same way.
Okay.
This way, we have roughly done the effect of this pants.
And is our waist flat here?
All the affected parts are in our pants.
Here.
Then if you feel that the position of this pleat is a little bit inward,
then we can move it a little bit outward.
Okay.
After moving outward,
because our line has moved,
but the dorsal line has not moved, right?
So we have to re-create the dorsal line.
Okay.
Here, this step is the same.
Turn left first.
Then turn the dorsal line into a turn.
Keep doing it.
Do it in the same way.
We won't show you here.
Okay.
Then.
For the side,
you can need it.
Give him a dead point here on the knee.
After hitting the knee point,
we keep the curve of this side curve in this pants.
Then,
I'll tighten this point.
This will be a little bit like radish.
Or like the radish pants, the soles of the feet are a little tighter here.
Then there is another point, I looked at the reference effect.
I think its pants are generally loose and wide.
This point needs to be explained to everyone.
Why is this pants like this?
In fact, in general, the pants are relatively close to each other.
Why is the pants like this in the MV?
It's because in the 20th century, it was popular to wear pants like this.
It's more popular.
The upper body feels like it's going to fight.
This is what we call braiding.
Braiding looks more like...
It's more casual.
The lower body is more relaxed.
It looks more relaxed and chill.
I saw that the staff said that the lower body should also be braided.
A small tip.
For the pants, you don't have to do it in the pants.
It's not going to be braided.
Because the length of the pants is very long on the side.
It's different from your clothes.
The clothes are short.
The clothes are very...
It's very different from the pants.
But the rise and fall of the pants is very small.
So usually our pants are in the lower half.
Especially in the lower half.
You don't need the so-called rope.
Do you understand?
Because your curve is long enough.
You don't need to use the rope to make up for the problem on the side.
And then we can...
Because in the middle of the knee, we made an end point here.
See?
This point is these two points.
Then we change this foot alone.
It won't affect the wide and loose in the middle.
It will only affect the corner of the foot.
We adjust it little by little according to this effect.
Then try to make it symmetrical left and right.
In fact, to make a tight and close board.
And here, why do I use this original curve tool?
Because just now we have a very obvious corner here.
Understand?
We just had a very obvious corner.
It's because there are two curves here.
There are two straight lines here.
See?
There is a corner here.
It's more obvious here.
This corner is because we both have this breakpoint.
Then you sew the line together.
This point is protruding out.
We use an original curve tool here.
Make a corner here.
Just round it up.
Look at the curve on the side.
Now there is no strange straight line.
Then you can make it longer according to your needs.
I think it's almost done.
It seems that there is no longer.
Of course.
Oh, yes.
I still make it longer.
Yes.
Why do I make it longer here?
I don't know if you just found it.
When I made it longer,
did I wear the pants together with the shoes?
When you are making clothes,
do you feel that your shoes seem to eat the fabric?
Right?
It feels like your fabric,
as long as it passes through the shoes or the hair,
it will be hooked.
First of all, let me explain why.
It's because of our model.
For example, there are shoes on the hair.
First of all, its grid is relatively small.
Secondly, its interior is there.
When your board passes through these structures,
even if the board passes through the human body,
it will touch the back of the hair line.
Once it touches the back of the hair line,
and when the grid of this part is relatively small,
the board will not be able to detect this bump.
It can't be
out of the model.
Sometimes you will find that
in fact, it's not so important to touch the big body and the board.
It will simulate itself in a while.
It's because of the body of the person.
Its grid is usually neat.
Or its grid will not be so small.
It can be touched.
Because the board has its own particle structure.
Do you understand?
So if your board has a smaller particle structure,
it's easier for you to pull it out.
Because your grid has enough space.
It's enough to bounce out.
It has more volume.
So what did I choose here?
I reduced the frictional shrinkage of this board.
In other words,
the frictional shrinkage of this board is reduced.
it's equivalent to
wearing a short pair of pants first.
This way I can prevent
the frictional shrinkage of the board
from causing the grid and the shoes to be intertwined.
Do you understand?
I took this step first.
I put on the pants first.
Just like when I do this
multi-layer wear and wear.
I will choose to turn the board into a tight one.
This way I can prevent the frictional shrinkage of the board first.
Do you understand?
So I used a frictional shrinkage here.
You can see that
our frictional shrinkage here is 90.
Then this pants becomes a weird short pants.
Then we stretch the pants.
Ah, right, right.
Hello, CG Ma Chui Chui.
I also recommend you today.
The video in MD
where you tie the board and transform it.
The video is pretty good.
I also recommend you to pay attention to it.
Please pay attention to Ma Chui Chui.
OK.
Then we return the frictional shrinkage to 100.
The pants will naturally be worn
and stacked on the shoes of the virtual model.
Because it is not intertwined with the grid.
Then it won't have this kind of
instability that can't be removed.
OK.
As for the side,
I just thought its effect was a bit exaggerated.
So I think
I should choose one of the lines on the side.
Move it all the way in.
Because do you remember?
The part above this point,
the waist here,
we are all done.
It's symmetrical.
Right?
Ah, right, right.
Then we move the middle part
to adjust its effect.
The teacher is here.
OK.
Then we put the shirt
that we saved before.
And then we put the hem of the shirt in.
A small tip.
The progress is already half way through.
Everyone sit down quickly.
Correct, correct.
OK.
We pour the clothes we stored before in.
First of all,
The part of our pants.
Ah, we first reverse the fire of this pants.
The plate and vermicelli line
Because the pants and this top and both top and bottom
马甲和马甲都有穿插,如果这个时候我们冷冻裤子,这个裤子是不是就会影响到衣服和马甲,对不对?
因为最后这个裤子它是穿在衬衫外面,但是它是在马甲里面的,明白了吗?
嗯,如果你要选,就是如果你要想学做跟现实生活中对接的衣服的话,你可以关注一下,关注一下Clo,就是C-L-O,我们公司的另外一块软件,跟服装对接的软件。
哎呀,谢谢CJ嘛,垂垂。
哎,垂垂以后可以做我们的下一期。
嗯。
下一期直播的嘉宾。
啊,好,我们反激活的裤子,哎,我再回来考一下,刚刚有讲过啊,我们为什么要反激活裤子呀?
我们为什么要反激活裤子呢?
没错啊,雅久森派医学部,避免冲突。
对,对对,因为有穿插啊,我们反激活的裤子这样就不会有穿插了,接下去我们就单独激活衬衫。
马甲这里我们先让它冷冻着啊,好。
衬衫这里呢,我们就给衬衫先加一下缩滤,再让它变成紧身衬衫。
或者说啊,我们的袖子这里,因为和裤子没有穿插,所以说不影响。
我们可以直接冷冻袖子,只选择大身的这几个版片。
有没有发现我没有选门筋啊?因为门筋上面有扭扣。
如果你把门筋也一起,就是加缩滤的话,这个扭扣容易不稳定。
小知识。
所以我通常加缩滤的时候呢,我不会选那个门筋。
好。
这里我们把它的尾向缩滤,就是大身的尾向缩滤。
我们可以改成80,这样它就变成紧身的。
对不对?
那马甲还是在靠外的位置嘛。
所以我们现在就,哎,冷冻这个内层的服装版片。
然后激活这个,嗯。
这里我们先给所有的马甲上层级,上一个2的层级。
然后最里面的这一层,我们不用去改它的层级。
接着我们把裤子给激活。
这个裤子这里的话,我们给它一个,嗯。
我们先把马甲给反激活了。
因为我最后想了一下,这个马甲位置,如果我激活的话,可能还是会有一点不稳定。
所以我们一层一层来,一点一点来。
我们先选择裤子版片,然后把裤子的层级设置为1。
然后开启模拟,模拟一下。
好。
模拟完了之后,现在裤子是不是穿在了衬衫的外面。
而且它现在是稳定的。
好。
所以我们就冷冻了裤子。
再激活马甲。
激活马甲之后,我们按空格键模拟一下。
因为马甲层级是2,裤子层级是1。
所以裤子在层级为0的衬衫的外面,但是在层级为2的马甲的里面。
那这样我们就穿好了。
穿好了之后呢,就激活这一些版片。
让它们都互相去模拟一下。
嗯。
好,谢谢,谢谢大家。
好,谢谢。
然后最后我们把层级设置为0。
关于这个裆布怎么做,还有口袋怎么做的话,我们大家可以看以前的视频。
以前的视频都有讲过。
包括口袋怎么做,在最近新出的这个口袋教学视频当中也有。